# Anastasia Yaskevich

## Android Developer

Minsk, Belarus anastasia.yaskevich@gmail.com +375 (29) 352-69-32

### **SUMMARY**

I am Android developer for 1.5 years and 5 years in software engineering in total. Worked both as solo developer and in a team, supported existing apps and created new ones from scratch. Also have remote work experience. Familiar with such tools as Jira, Git, Figma, Invision. English level is Upper Intermediate.

#### **EDUCATION**

09/2011 — 06/2016

## **Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics**

Specialist's Degree in Computer Systems and Networks. Got specialization of Sotfware for Information Technologies.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

06/2019 — current

## Android Developer at SolbegSoft

Development of an SDK for a social video mobile application from scratch. Refactoring of the main app. Used Kotlin, MVICore, Clean Architecture, Retrofit, RxJava 2, Toothpick. Team: 4 developers and 2 QA.

11/2018 — 03/2019

## **Android Developer at iFuture**

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile application. Used Kotlin, MVI, Clean Architecture, Retrofit, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, JUnit and Mockito. Done part of performance optimization of UI. Team: 6 developers, 2 QA, 2 designers.

03/2018 — 11/2018

## **Android Developer at iFuture**

Development and refactoring of a client mobile application. Used Kotlin, Retrofit, Room, RxJava 2, Dagger 2, MVP, Clean Architecture. Took part in implementation of Form Decorator (transformed JSON of field appearance description into UI) and implemented demo app. Team: 2 developers, 2 QA and a designer.

*07/2016 — 03/2018* 

## Frontend Developer at iFuture

Development and refactoring of a betting mobile web application on React.js and ES6, Redux. Support of Android wrapper app on Crosswalk. Team: 8 developers, 4 QA and a designer.

*11/2015 — 07/2016* 

## **Groovy Developer at iFuture**

Development and refactoring of a large betting web application and a CMS. Used Groovy & Grails, MySQL, CoffeeScript, AngularJS, Redis. Team: 6 developers, 4 QA.

02/2015 — 11/2015

## **Junior Groovy Developer at REID Consulting**

Creating small web apps including frontend part from scratch. Used Groovy & Grails and Jenkins as CI. Worked alone but had code review by a mentor.